The Shawshank Redemption
The Godfather
The Godfather: Part II
The Dark Knight
12 Angry Men
Schindler's List
The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King
Pulp Fiction
The Good, the Bad and the Ugly
The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring
Fight Club
Forrest Gump
Inception
Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back
The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers
The Matrix
Goodfellas
One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest
Seven Samurai
Se7en
Life Is Beautiful
City of God
The Silence of the Lambs
It's a Wonderful Life
Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope
Saving Private Ryan
Spirited Away
The Green Mile
Parasite
Interstellar
LΘon: The Professional
Hamilton
The Usual Suspects
Harakiri
The Lion King
Back to the Future
The Pianist
Terminator 2: Judgment Day
American History X
Modern Times
Psycho
Gladiator
City Lights
The Departed
The Intouchables
Whiplash
The Prestige
Grave of the Fireflies
Once Upon a Time in the West
Casablanca
Cinema Paradiso
Rear Window
Alien
Apocalypse Now
Memento
Raiders of the Lost Ark
The Great Dictator
Joker
Django Unchained
The Lives of Others
Paths of Glory
The Shining
WALL╖E
Avengers: Infinity War
Sunset Blvd.
Witness for the Prosecution
Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse
Princess Mononoke
Oldboy
Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb
The Dark Knight Rises
Once Upon a Time in America
Aliens
Avengers: Endgame
Your Name.
Coco
American Beauty
Braveheart
3 Idiots
Das Boot
Toy Story
High and Low
Amadeus
Taare Zameen Par
Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi
Inglourious Basterds
Reservoir Dogs
Good Will Hunting
Capernaum
2001: A Space Odyssey
Requiem for a Dream
Vertigo
M
Dangal
Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind
1917
The Hunt
Citizen Kane
Full Metal Jacket
Bicycle Thieves
The Kid
A Clockwork Orange
North by Northwest
Snatch
Singin' in the Rain
Scarface
Taxi Driver
Ikiru
AmΘlie
Lawrence of Arabia
Toy Story 3
The Sting
Metropolis
A Separation
For a Few Dollars More
Incendies
The Apartment
Double Indemnity
Come and See
To Kill a Mockingbird
Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade
Up
L.A. Confidential
Heat
Monty Python and the Holy Grail
Die Hard
Rashomon
Yojimbo
Batman Begins
Green Book
Downfall
Children of Heaven
Unforgiven
Anand
Some Like It Hot
Ran
Howl's Moving Castle
A Beautiful Mind
All About Eve
The Great Escape
Casino
Pan's Labyrinth
The Wolf of Wall Street
The Secret in Their Eyes
Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels
My Neighbor Totoro
Raging Bull
There Will Be Blood
Judgment at Nuremberg
The Treasure of the Sierra Madre
Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri
My Father and My Son
Dial M for Murder
The Gold Rush
Chinatown
Shutter Island
V for Vendetta
No Country for Old Men
The Seventh Seal
Inside Out
Warrior
The Elephant Man
Trainspotting
The Sixth Sense
The Thing
Jurassic Park
Gone with the Wind
Wild Strawberries
The Truman Show
Finding Nemo
Blade Runner
Room
The Bridge on the River Kwai
Stalker
Kill Bill: Vol. 1
Fargo
Tokyo Story
The Third Man
On the Waterfront
Memories of Murder
Gran Torino
The Deer Hunter
Wild Tales
Klaus
Andhadhun
In the Name of the Father
Mary and Max
Gone Girl
Hacksaw Ridge
The Grand Budapest Hotel
The Big Lebowski
Before Sunrise
Catch Me If You Can
The Bandit
Persona
Ford v Ferrari
To Be or Not to Be
Prisoners
The General
How to Train Your Dragon
Sherlock Jr.
Mr. Smith Goes to Washington
12 Years a Slave
Barry Lyndon
Mad Max: Fury Road
Network
Stand by Me
Million Dollar Baby
Cool Hand Luke
Ben-Hur
Hachi: A Dog's Tale
Dead Poets Society
Into the Wild
Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2
Platoon
The Wages of Fear
Logan
Monty Python's Life of Brian
Rush
The Handmaiden
Rififi
The 400 Blows
The Passion of Joan of Arc
Andrei Rublev
Hotel Rwanda
Spotlight
Amores Perros
NausicaΣ of the Valley of the Wind
La Haine
Rang De Basanti
Rocky
Gangs of Wasseypur
Monsters, Inc.
Rebecca
Portrait of a Lady on Fire
Before Sunset
In the Mood for Love
It Happened One Night
Drishyam
Paris, Texas
The Circus
The Invisible Guest
The Help
The Princess Bride
The Battle of Algiers
The Terminator
Three Colors: Red
A Silent Voice: The Movie
Swades
Throne of Blood
